It has happened that
in my childhood, I used to play doctor doctor.
She enjoyed checking up everyone at home.
I always thought that this is all a
game.
Now, we all are going to New Delhi to study. So, we will
stay with my childhood friend. Then we will take a house
on rent and our own small and big
houses will be built. And it will take seven-eight years for everything to be built. So
why take a house on rent?
[Music]
You don't know that you
can take a loan to buy a house by mortgaging your land. So, you are
right. For HDFC home loan,
farmers do not need to mortgage their agricultural land.
Home loans come here
on a long tenure of 20 years. With small MI, you will
easily have your own house in the city.
Remember, it is not mandatory for farmers to file income tax returns to take HDFC Rural Loans
and farmers do
not need to mortgage their agricultural land.
Do that.